gucci.com 2015-03-02

# Gucci - assistance

Revised as of September 2014

This website is provided and managed by Gucci America, Inc. 

Gucci recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal and financial information. We have instituted reasonable policies and security measures to protect the information you provide to us. When you register online with Gucci, use our online store, or choose to fill out and submit one of our customer information cards when visiting a Gucci store, you give us your consent to process and use such submitted personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. 

This privacy policy applies to all protected personal information collected, maintained or used by Gucci. “Gucci” means Gucci America, Inc. and Guccio Gucci S.P.A. (Florence, Via Tornabuoni 73/r - Italy), which is the ultimate data controller. Gucci is an affiliate of the [Kering Group](http://www.kering.com/). 

#### What Information Gucci Collects

Gucci collects some protected personal information (e.g. name, address, telephone number(s), email address, etc.) from visitors to its website who register their information or who use the online store. We also use cookies (as described below) and track IP addresses so that we can improve our services and enhance your Gucci experience. In addition, Gucci collects some protected personal information from our customers who submit a customer information card at one of our stores, from our affiliated companies and, on occasion, from online or offline third party sources. We may use any such personal information about our customers and prospective customers in order to better serve you and to enhance the promotional offerings, tailored advertisements and communications you receive. 

Gucci does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen, please ask your parents to register and/or use the online store. 

#### How Gucci Uses Information You Provide

The data that you choose to provide to us at one of our stores or online, and the data that we may collect, is used by Gucci to keep you informed of our special events or promotions, to register you with our website, to administer our website services, and/or to process any orders you may place online. Otherwise, we may use the information you provide to us only to review our performance and to improve our services to you, or to communicate with you about your order if you have placed an online order. 

Gucci maintains customer data for purposes of customer relationship management, marketing research, analysis and promotion. By either giving the appropriate consent on our website or by submitting your email address on a customer information card, you agree that Gucci may send you announcements on products or promotions, tailored advertisements that may be of particular interest to you, and invitations to Gucci’s events based on your purchase profile. 

If you provide incomplete or inaccurate data, Gucci may be unable to inform you of specific promotions or events and to provide you with our services. 

#### Does Gucci Share Your Information With Others?

Gucci does not sell, rent or, except as described below, disclose our client's names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information to any non-Kering Group entity. Gucci may share customer information within Kering Group, so that you may be informed of other products that may be of interest to you. 

Your data will be held in our secured electronic Worldwide Gucci Customer Database which may be accessed by other companies within the Kering Group throughout the world and by selected third-party service providers acting on Gucci’s behalf. 

In order to maintain our website, to manage our database, and to distribute and provide promotional materials and other communications to clients or potential clients, Gucci contracts with selected third parties. As necessary, the personal information you provide to us may be processed by these third parties, solely on Gucci’s behalf but we do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use of your information. 

Gucci does not otherwise disclose your information to third parties, unless we are required to do so by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding. If Gucci is acquired by another entity or is merged or consolidated, information about Gucci customers may be made available to the new entity. However, the new entity will agree to protect the confidentiality of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

#### Security

Gucci uses appropriate security measures to protect the information you provide to us. However, while we take reasonable steps to protect this personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, you accept that no Internet data transmission can be guaranteed to be secure from access by unintended recipients and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this breach is due to our negligence. 

#### Accuracy and Retention

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all personal data you provide us, or to remove your name from the Gucci’s marketing list at any time by contacting gucci.com at 877.482.2430 or by contacting us at the email or mailing address listed below. If you are registered with Gucci on our website and would like us to remove you from our marketing list, please click on this unsubscribe link. 

#### About Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information a web site can send to your computer's browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our web site more user friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the website. For example, cookies allow us to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you do not have to accept them. To disable cookies, you should access the "help" tab on your browser or read the information that came with your browser software. However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if cookies are not disabled. If you do not disable your cookies, you accept our collection and storage of any of your personal information such cookies contain. 

#### Acceptance of Privacy Policy and Modifications

By accessing and using the Gucci website (including registering on the website or purchasing items through our website), or by submitting a customer information card at a Gucci store, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. Gucci reserves the right occasionally to make changes to our privacy policy or practices. We will post the updated policy on our website, and thus we encourage you to review this page from time to time, particularly each time you use our online shop. 

If you are registered with us and would like to delete your registration and personal details from our database, please click on this unsubscribe link. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries regarding our privacy policy or to update, correct or request removal of your personal information from our Customers Database, please write to Gucci Online Shopping, 685 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY 10022 or e-mail us at: [privacy@us.gucci.com](mailto:privacy@us.gucci.com).
